Babatunde Ololade

Software Developer

Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey +905466425485 babatundeololade50@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative and self-starting Software Engineer with 3 years experience of building scalable apps and website of various kinds. In terms of frontend, React is a library that I have mastered. Besides that, I have an idea about Angular, Svelte and testing is one of my core skills. I love following fashion and standards in the UI / UX space. I spend a lot of time on researching about the latest trend in the web development industry.

MORE LINKS

folio/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/babat unde-ololade-7a9179a7/ https://github.com/Babatunde50 https://twitter.com/tundejs

https://babatunde50.github.io/port

FOCUS SKILLS

JavaScript, React/React Native, MongoDB, Express, HTML/CSS, Nodejs, GraphQL, Problem Solving, Human Relations ..and Medium Article Writing:)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bukooh - Lead Engineer

January 2017 - July 2019

Developing customer-oriented websites. All processes from planning and implementation of the project.

CloudWare - Fulll Stack Developer

April 2020 - May 2020

I developed scalable webs apps and interfaces using HTML, CSS, and PHP. I helped speed up the time it took to take the product to market and hereby increase the revenue of the company

Truparse – *Software Engineer*

Jun 2020 - Oct 2020

- I turn prototypes into real apps.
- Collaborating with designers to ensure designs were efficient and technically sound
- Leveraging responsive web frameworks to complete deliverables ahead of schedule
- Conducting A/B testing to identify bugs and UI improvements

Convre – Lead Frontend Developer

Oct 2020 - Present

- Recommending solutions for a streamlined, user-friendly interface with the design team.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.
- Building stable and maintainable codebases using React
- Leveraging responsive web frameworks to complete deliverables ahead of schedule

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

 ${\bf Halic\ University,}\ {\bf Istanbul,}\ {\bf Turkey-Software\ Engineering}$

2021 - Present

 ${\bf University\ of\ Ibadan,\ Oyo\ State,\ Nigeria-{\it Computer\ Science}}$

2020